hyundai.co.uk 2005-12-18

# Hyundai | Privacy

Hyundai Motor UK Ltd and its group companies take the privacy of your information very seriously. We aim to meet current Internet best practice. Our services are designed to give you the information that you want to receive. Our Privacy Policy below explains how we will collect and use the information you give us. We may vary this policy from time to time and the current version will be that published on this site. The word 'we' refers to Hyundai Motor UK Ltd, unless otherwise indicated.

* Collecting your information 

From time to time, you will be asked to submit personal information about yourself (e.g. name and email address etc) in order to receive or use services on our website. These services include newsletters and competitions, live chats and message boards and personalised services. We will also need personal information in order to supply other products and services or to help us identify you when you contact us. When we collect this information we will only do so over a secure connection. If you communicate with us by email over the internet you should be aware that the nature of the internet is such that unencrypted communication may not be secure and may pass through several different countries on route to us. Please do not email us with confidential or sensitive information such as your credit card details. We cannot accept responsibility for unauthorised access to your information that is outside our control. 

We may combine this information with other information that we may hold about you if you are a RAC customer, or have made enquiries of us before. We may also obtain information from publicly available sources such as the electoral roll, or other third parties who have a legitimate basis on which to pass on your information.

We will act in accordance with current legislation and we will provide a link to our Data Protection Notice every time we invite you to submit personal information to us. Our Data Protection Notice is given below.

## RAC Data Protection Notice

Hyundai Motor UK Ltd will share the information you provide, together with other information, with our group companies*. We (RAC group companies) will use this for administration, marketing, customer services and profiling your purchasing preferences. We will disclose your information to our service providers and agents for these purposes. We may keep your information for a reasonable period to contact you about our services. For information about the way we use cookies and other web tracking devices please refer to section 2 in this privacy policy. 

We may transfer your information outside of the European Economic Area, for example to Asia. We will only do this where it is necessary for the conclusion, or performance of a contract between us, or that we enter into at your request, in your interest, or for administrative, or our own marketing purposes.

When you give us information about another person, you confirm that they have authorised you to act for them, to consent to the processing and use of their personal data in the manner described in this notice and to receive on their behalf any data protection notice.

You have the right to ask for a copy of your information (for which we will charge a small fee) and to correct any inaccuracies.

We may record telephone calls for staff training and evidential purposes.

### Informing you about products and services

We offer motoring and travel related products such as breakdown services, hotel bookings and vehicle inspections, sales and leasing. We also offer financial products such as Insurance, loans and credit cards. We may also share your information with our business partners. By submitting data to us, you will be indicating to us and our business partners, your consent to us and them, contacting you by mail, telephone, fax, email, and SMS/MMS to let you know about any goods, services or promotions of our own our business partners or other third parties, which may be of interest to you unless you indicate an objection to receiving such messages by ticking the box provided.

### Sensitive data

By submitting data to us, you give us consent to use your sensitive personal data e.g. health data for your registration under the Motability Scheme (if appropriate), solely for the purposes for which you submit it.

(*Hyundai Motor UK Ltd is part of RAC plc, which includes the Lex group of companies, and the British School of Motoring Limited.

back to top

* How we collect information about your visits to our website 

When you visit our web pages, we will download something called a 'cookie' to your computer (section 7). We may also collect information using web beacons (also known as clear gifs or web bugs - see section 10). Our cookies and Web Beacons provide us with non-personal statistical information about what you do on the website. For example: the duration of time a page was viewed, common paths taken through the site, data on screen settings and other general information. We may also collect information about what other websites you visit after ours. We use this data to improve the services on our site and to refine your experience of using our sites.

* What we will do with your personal information 

We will only use your information for the purposes that you would reasonably anticipate or that we state when we collect it and, where necessary, for which you have given us your consent. We will not contact you, or pass your information to our business partners, for marketing purposes unless you have indicated your agreement that we may do so.

Where we are making arrangements on your behalf we may need to pass your information to third parties to conclude those arrangements. For example, to a hotel to make a hotel booking, or to an insurance company to obtain insurance quotes.

We are committed to treating your personal data with due care and in accordance with the data protection principles.

* Sensitive information 

In the Data Protection Notice above we refer to the collection of sensitive data. In addition to the example given we will also collect other sensitive data when providing you with insurance quotations and policies. This is information relating to your health generally and also to any relevant convictions. We pass information, which may include this sensitive data, to the insurance companies from whom we obtain quotations. We, and they, only use this information to provide you with quotations and insurance. We will not be able to provide you with quotes, without this sensitive data.

back to top

* How to access your personal information 

Please address requests to the Data Protection Compliance Manager, Hyundai Motor UK Ltd 17 Connaught Place, London W2 2EL. (Please note that a small fee of å£10.00 will be charged for dealing with these requests). If you believe that any of the data we hold about you is incorrect or being misused or want further information you may contact us at the above address.

* Users aged 16 and under 

If you are 16 or under you must have permission from a parent or guardian before you give us personal information. If we find that we have received information from you without the appropriate consent, we reserve the right to cancel all transactions and services and remove all personal data that you have supplied. You will be able to re-submit the information when you have the required permission.

* What is a cookie? 

Cookies are text files that identify your computer (through what is known as an IP address) to our server. For information about what we use these for refer to section 2. Whilst in some cases it may be possible, we do not use the IP address as a means of identifying you. You generally have the opportunity to set your computer to accept all cookies, to notify you when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. You can do this through your internet browser. With most browsers, this facility can be reached via the 'tools' (e.g. Internet Explorer), or 'edit', or "task" (e.g. Netscape) menu. If you have any problems finding this area, the 'help' function within your browser will be able to provide assistance. You can also find more detailed information about cookies and how to manage them on <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>.

If you refuse a cookie it may prevent the proper operation of the site or even prevent your access to certain areas.

* What is a Web Beacon? 

Some of our Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes known as clear gifs) that allow us to count users who have visited these pages. Web beacons collect only limited information that includes a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides. These beacons do not carry any personally identifiable information and are only used to track the effectiveness of our site or particular campaigns.

You can find more information on Web Beacons, their use and your rights, if you visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy or any other aspect of our data handling procedures, please contact us via the address below, marking all correspondence for the attention of the Data Protection Compliance Manager.

* Links to other websites 

Our Websites may contain links to other sites outside the group. Neither Hyundai Motor UK Ltd, nor its group companies, are responsible for the privacy and security of these sites. This privacy policy applies only to this website.

back to top
